const easyQuestions = [{
        question: "What is the name of Harry's Owl?",
        a: "Scabbers",
        b: "Hedwig",
        c: "Trevor",
        d: "Nagini",
        answer: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of Harry's parents?",
        a: "Lily & James",
        b: "Nymphadora & ",
        c: "Arthur & Molly",
        d: "Frank & Lily",
        answer: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the (real) name of the wizard that killed Harry's parents?",
        a: "Severus Snape",
        b: "Bellatrix Lestrange",
        c: "Lucius Malfoy",
        d: "Tom Riddle",
        answer: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Harry go to School?",
        a: "Durmstrang",
        b: "Beaxbatons",
        c: "Hogwarts School of witchcraft and wizardry",
        d: "Castelobruxo",
        answer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the train that takes the students to the Hogwarts?",
        a: "Kings Cross Express",
        b: "Hogwarts Express",
        c: "Hogwarts train",
        d: "Kings Express",
        answer: "b",
    },
];

const mediumQuestions = [{
        question: "How many books did J.K Rowling publish in the Harry Potter universe?",
        a: "5",
        b: "6",
        c: "7",
        d: "8",
        answer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of He Who Must Not Be Named's snake?",
        a: "Salazar",
        b: "Herpo",
        c: "Nagini",
        d: "Morfin",
        answer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "What are Hermione's parents muggle proffession?",
        a: "Dentists",
        b: "Doctors",
        c: "Physiotherapists",
        d: "Hair dressers",
        answer: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "What does Lucius Malfoy slip Ginny Weasley in the second film?",
        a: "A letter",
        b: "A napkin",
        c: "A diary",
        d: "A wand",
        answer: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "What animal does Harry help set free in the third movie or book?",
        a: "A Grindilow",
        b: "A Dragon",
        c: "A Spider",
        d: "A Hippogriff",
        answer: "d",
    },
]

const hardQuestions = [{
        question: "What spell is used the most in the Harry potter universe?",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ron's oldest brother?",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Harry's godfather?",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        question: "What type of animagus is Professor McGonagall?",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        question: "In what city is St Mungos Hospital for Maladies and Injuries?",
        a: "",
        b: "",
        c: "",
        d: "",
        answer: "",
    },
];